Inventory of the Clarissa Sligh Papers, 1950-2012
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2012-0149),1985-2012, (35 boxes)
  - Masculinity Project Part 2 of 3 (11x14 black and white prints) (Box 103)
  - Masculinity Project Part 3 of 3 (11x14 black and white prints) (Box 103)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 103)
  - Jake in Transition (11x14 black and white prints) (Box 103)
  - Masculinity Project- Gallery Prints (Box 103)
  - Jake in Transition booklets (Box 104)
  - List of Slaves at Ashlawn, 1838 (Box 104)
  - Jake in Transition (Box 104)
  - Wrongly Bodied Two (Box 104)
  - Miscellaneous (Negatives and Transparencies) (Box 105)
  - Unlabled Artwork (Box 106)
  - Fold-out book (Box 106)
  - Coast to Coast Poster (Box 106)
  - An American Girl (Box 106)
  - Women Bring the People (Box 106)
  - Iran Control Connection, 1988 (Box 106)
  - Mao Tse-Tung (Box 106)
  - Marian Anderson (Box 106)
  - Born in Flames (Box 106)
  - Faith Ringgold (Box 106)
  - FMLN (Box 106)
  - Quarter to Armageddon (Box 106)
  - We've Carried the Rich for 200 years (Box 106)
  - Captain Ileana (Box 106)
  - Stop U.S. Intervention in Central America (Box 106)
  - Women's Caucus for Art Exhibitions (Box 106)
  - Encuentro International Sindieal Por la Paz (Box 106)
  - Journada de la Independencia (Box 106)
  - Sahara Occujdental (Box 106)
  - Farabundoes (Box 106)
  - Lumumba (Box 106)
  - Saudi Arabia-Guerilla Girls (Box 106)
  - New York is Book Country (Box 106)
  - What's Happening With Momma? (Box 106)
  - Chile and No Mipetes Posters (Box 106)
  - No Business as Usual (Box 106)
  - Stop U.S. Intervention in Central America (Box 106)
  - Guerilla Girls (Box 106)
  - The Abortion Project (Box 106)
  - Art Workers Coalition (Box 106)
  - The Secret (Box 106)
  - Where is Ana Mendieta? (Box 106)
  - Jane Played With Dick, Dick Played With Spot (Box 106)
  - Barn Theatre and Laundryman's Daughter (Box 106)
  - Image Used for "Plaintiff Speaks" Essay (Box 107)
  - U.S. Naval Training, Jan. 1953 (features Sligh's brother, Carroll Thompson) (Box 107)
  - Robert Oppenheimer, Hampton, 1957 (Box 107)
  - Art Journals (Box 108)
  - Guerilla Girls (Poster, Sticker, and Cards) (Box 108)
  - Lillian Thompson: Portrait of Tammy (Christmas, 1970) (Box 108)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 108)
  - 1953- High School Trip to the U.N., and 1972- Skowhegan School Class Photo (Box 108)
  - Family Photos and Snapshots (Box 108)
  - Self-Portraits made during Paris residency, 1990s (Box 108)
  - What's Happening With Momma? House Model (Box 108)
  - What's Happening With Momma? House Model 2 (Box 108)
  - What's Happening With Momma? (Box 109)
  - Coast to Coast: A Woman of Color National Artist's Project (Box 109)
  - Coast to Coast: Artist's Project (Portfolio) (Box 109)
  - Handbook of Practical Geographies; artists' book by Heather O'Hara, Women's Studio Workshop, 2004. (Box 110)
  - Series of 6 prints on fabric of images from Reframing the Past, 1987 (Box 110)
  - Untitled (For Momma), 2002. Triptych, with wall installation instructions. (Box 111)
  - Collaborations with E.J. Montgomery (Box 112)
  - 11x14 black and white watercolor self-portraits, 1993 (Box 112)
  - Reframing the Past (Box 113)
  - Aaron Roseman Research Materials (Box 114)
  - Photographs of Aaron Roseman (Box 114)
  - 1957 Graduating Class- Clarissa Sligh (Box 115)
  - Articles from Virginia Desegregation Trials, 1984 (Box 115)